i'm starting you out for you
and me
and i say that when the sky fall
when the sky fall a一里面一个
you hear the sign
唉可能掉了死了死
没血了
to tell you
i love you
i will be
ok
i run to the moon and what about the sea
黑口黑口黑口黑口了吗
我把带了先放下来啊
can you play the siren
so together
we can wait to the wall
can you hear the siren
call that you
don't know
'cause i'll save you
want the sky fall
about things out of my kind of ha sa
牛逼牛逼牛逼牛逼
hold on the
now
we fight as one once again
together
how long
it's so strong
完美控枪手自己
死了死了没没有过
没事了没事了
天空
发展的地方
这地方不发展就发展了个法子呀
上了高一点
等一下能不能打就会走b洞了
我死了死了死了
别控了别控了
you running away from away from me
懂吗懂吗懂吗
a a a a a a爆掉爆掉爆掉
我好烦呀
我要死了
又没有又
holding holding your tongue with me
走这个走这个三明治一样
没事没
好好好哎
就是三分不出来
这俩队友没钱啊
左手看他俩
拆他俩
二楼一个
我在知道
hello
i can not put that on your mind
you like a sabotage of your time
sa
要闪吗
你啊要闪吗
不要了
不要什么什么成本
看不懂我
推完去了
你跟你逼逼逼
怎么搞
不管赢了
哈哈哈哈哈
好没事了
他没打我吧
嗯哼哎哎呦
我都被打傻了
这波打的是人进门啊
哎呦进门就是卖队友
哎呦赢了四kv 6
所以说你慢点斜坡一个好吧
就这样把你砍他对it is not too
it is to hear
you can't let you go
i can do this again
oh i can't see you for your be
在一can't keep you
but i'm sai
帮助你帮助他
他帮助他帮助你
小俩号手上了
我架左边
我在前一秒在点一
别死别死
然后牛逼啊
我去真强
大闪开开
开个小车
三道四了
拆拆拆球跳跳
卧槽我去
i've been one with the hand that
i don't want to be
什么呀
这人keep you from home
but i'll set on fire to
keep you go on
and on my sin
fbi
can't keep you from home
ston i keep on
这还不赢了
剑剑剑剑一个剑剑杀了
来个大哎
连接连接一个连接所有链接
keep you from all
but i'm sour hard to keep you
i can't go on my own
sd hito
keep you on
i keep keep you
下把要没事没事
就你那有狙高坡高坡高坡有狙a2 楼
很快你能打到我这边了
哎他打我了
又到了
这小龙一个死了一把pa k快快快来
k a k
嗯装起来
我和你的
卧槽卧槽卧槽卧槽卧槽
回去了回去了
打中人打中人
还有一个看
还有一个你看好听
超市有一个黄色
好在我没闪闪光
闪光下
又不能打野大杀一个中路
三个
逼他逼他逼他
大哥别狙
准备狙击
准备狙
好好打
我架着架着你走了走了
可我的孩子没有
see you know you
哎呦
没人帮我这个人啊
be a le
温暖的那一刻
等待你的喜好
不自以为走走走
cd cd cd cd好
牛逼牛逼
那雷摔到了他摔到他脚底下了
然后被人他妈一穿二
近点呀
你
第二枪
我感觉是从右边来的
okay
i got in my humble
ne to make me
feel that i won't stop
oh we got this gime devil
you just moni
不要一个me do
一就一颗一颗爱情的我的你忘
啊
那你看看能不能多开开
看看能否在的彩虹弄
我心中能找到
下一个不想抱走吧抱走吧
static former yi love your life
和你一边不安
哎呀一
推吧推吧推吧
你要我不能和你一起的胸膛
月色之心